# List of questions 
questions = [
    {
        'question' : 'Which of the following is used to declare a function in python',
        'options' : ['1.function', '2.def', '3.print'],
        'answers' : '2'
    },
    {
        'question' : 'The difference between a list and a dict is ',
        'options' : ['1.Immutability', '2.arrangement', '3.Ordering'],
        'answers' : '3'
    },
    {
        'question' : 'What is the difference between list and a tuple',
        'options' : ['1.Immutability', '2. Ordering', '3.Displacement'],
        'answers' : '1'
    },
    {
        'question' : 'Which data type uses a key value pair',
        'options' : ['1.set', '2.dict', '3.lst'],
        'answers' : '2'
    },
    {
        'question' : 'The data-type that helps to eliminate duplicates of values in a list is called?:',
        'options' : ['1.Dict', '2.Set', '3.object'],
        'answers' : '2'
    },
    {
        'question' : 'This is an example of which data-type {1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6}',
        'options' : ['1.Dict', '2.object', '3.set'],
        'answers' : '3'
    },
    {
        'question' : 'A python file is recognised with an extension of?:',
        'options' : ['1..html', '2.py', '3..js'],
        'answers' : '2'
    },
    {
        'question' : ' x =5, y=20, result=20% 5, print(result)',
        'options' : ['1.1', '2.-1', '3.0'],
        'answers' : '3'
    },
    {
        'question' : 'set_a = {2 3, 4, 5} set_b={3, 4, 5, 6, 7},form_set =set_a & set_b, print(form_set) ',
        'options' : ['1.{2, 3, 4, 5,6}', '2.{3, 4, 5}', '3.{2, 3, 5}'],
        'answers' : '2'
    },
    {
        'question' : 'From the question above the  "&" shortcut key stands for what ',
        'options' : ['1.Difference', '2.Combination', '3.Intercession'],
        'answers' : '3'
    },
        ]